Contact

ccjj44r@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/janegiganti-095a17b4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care CCRN BLS

Certifications

Clinical Nurse Leader

Honors-Awards

Hudson Valley Magazine's Excellence In Nursing 2015

Jane Giganti

Nursing Professional Development Specialist at Vassar Brothers Medical Center - Nuvance

Poughkeepsie, New York

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Critical Care Nursing, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Cardiac Surgery Unit Advanced Life Support (CSU-ALS), Extracorporeal Life Support (ECLS) and Clinical Research. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's Degree focused in Clinical Nurse Leader from Sacred Heart University.

Experience

Nuvance Health Nursing Professional Development Specialist June 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) Poughkeepsie

Health Quest

Nursing Professional Development Specialist May 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)

Vassar Brothers Medical Center Poughkeepsie New York

Orange Regional Medical Center

12 years 10 months

Registered Nurse

October 2007 - Present (12 years 10 months)

Middletown, NY

MICU

Nursing Professional Development Specialist July 2015 - May 2018 (2 years 11 months)

Clinical education for RNs in both acute and critical care departments

Arden Hill Hospital RN

October 2000 - September 2006 (6 years)

Goshen, NY

ICU

Valley Health System

RN

June 1990 - September 2000 (10 years 4 months)

Ridgewood, NJ

RN, Clinical Coordinator

Education

Sacred Heart University

Master's Degree, Clinical Nurse Leader · (2015 - 2017)

Chamberlain College of Nursing

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2014)

SUNY Orange

Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1987 - 1990)